I'm afraid
you'll get in trouble
because of
my feelings for you
I heard it from Soobin
16 years ago
at the shooting set
the kid who came to see
me every day was you
Why haven't you
told me so far?
I don't know
I just…
Maybe I wanted
a fresh start
I didn't wanna
confuse you
with such things
I'm not confused
I like you too
[To Shin Yoo-il
Thank you, Lee Hyesung!]
What's this?
It's my autograph
Hey, what's this?
Four years ago
when the short film
was screened
you came to the theater
I got your autograph
at that time
It's unbelievable
What…
You really liked me
Hey, are you a stalker
or something?
Stalker? Come on
I was just a fan
But I remember
that moment
Really?
Yeah
That was my first
autograph
as an adult actor
I'd been thinking
of quitting acting, but
after autographing
my fan like that
I was motivated
to start over
I'm glad
I've been keeping it
It's Lee Hyesung's
first autograph, right?
I should keep it
as an heirloom
You liked me so much
It must've been hard
for you to hold it up
That's why I spit it out
that I like you